<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Willian Paixao</title>
    <link>https://willianpaixao.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Willian Paixao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 11:24:04 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://willianpaixao.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Impossible List</title>
      <link>https://willianpaixao.github.io/impossible-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 11:24:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://willianpaixao.github.io/impossible-list/</guid>
      <description>Totally based on College Info Geek&amp;rsquo;s post, I would like to build and maintain my own wish list of personal challenges.
Life  Read 1000 books. [progress] Write and self-publish a book Have enough money to retire (using the 4% rule)  Fitness  Earn a Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu black belt Do 100 push-ups in a single set Do 100 pull-ups in a single set Run 5km in under 25 minutes Run 10km in under 1 hour Run a half marathon Run a marathon Run an Ironman  Travel Travel list  Travel anywhere cool with my sister Bring my sister to Stockholm See the northern lights Bike through the Route1(Ring Road) in Iceland Visit Machu Picchu Visit Tokyo  Living  Live in Germany for at least 1 year Live in Italy for at least 1 year Live as nomad for at least 1 year  Professional Certifications  Renew my LPIC1 Pass the LPIC2 Renew my Goethe-Zertifikat B1 Pass the Goethe-Zertifikat B2 Complete German course on Duolingo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://willianpaixao.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 11:30:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://willianpaixao.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description> A Computer Engineer from Universidade Federal do Pará, born and raised in the Amazon rainforest region. Currently living in Stockholm and working at Ellmount Gaming as a DevOps Engineer.
When not working, I&amp;rsquo;m training Brazilian Jiu-jitsu.
Contact me  Professional
 Email // willian@ufpa.br Github // @willianpaixao LinkedIn // @willianpaixao  Personal
 Instagram // @willianpaixaoo Twitter // @willianpaixaoo   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tmux and Ansible</title>
      <link>https://willianpaixao.github.io/blog/tmux-ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 14:57:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://willianpaixao.github.io/blog/tmux-ansible/</guid>
      <description>Tmux is a &amp;ldquo;terminal multiplexer&amp;rdquo; that allows you to have multiples window terminals in a single terminal. And our beloved Ansible can help install and setup tmux.
Installing You need first install Tmux&amp;rsquo;s package. Among the several ways, we&amp;rsquo;ll just use the standard and offical package. This works for most of the operating systems.
- name: Install tmux package: name: tmux state: present tags: tmux  With just that you have a working tmux.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>